var jsonBreeds = `{
"id": 101,
"title": "Breeds",
"clues": [{
    "id": 2000,
    "answer": "Falabella",
    "question": "A breed of horse developed by a family in Argentina",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  },{
    "id": 2001,
    "answer": "Iowa",
    "question": "The American Cream Draft horse originated in this state",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  },{
    "id": 2002,
    "answer": "Appaloosa",
    "question": "A breed developed by the Nez Perce Indians",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  },{
    "id": 2003,
    "answer": "Clydesdale",
    "question": "A breed of large draught horse named after its area of origin in Scotland",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  },{
    "id": 2004,
    "answer": "American Quarter Horse",
    "question": "The most popular breed of horse in America",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  },{
    "id": 2005,
    "answer": "Appaloosa",
    "question": "Distinguishing characteristics of the breed are (1) Spotted coat pattern, (2) mottled skin, (3) white sclera, (4) vertically striped hooves",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  },{
    "id": 2006,
    "answer": "Welsh Pony",
    "question": "Breed of pony that originated in Wales",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  },{
    "id": 2007,
    "answer": "England",
    "question": "The history of the Thoroughbred horse began in this country",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  },{
    "id": 2008,
    "answer": "American Saddlebred",
    "question": "This current breed of horse is called the peacock of the horse world",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  },{
    "id": 2009,
    "answer": "Tennessee walking horse",
    "question": "The American Walking pony is a result of breeding the Welsh Pony and this breed",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  },{
    "id": 2010,
    "answer": "hinny",
    "question": "The result of breeding a Stallion and a female donkey",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  },{
    "id": 2011,
    "answer": "Arabian",
    "question": "The Thoroughbred was developed largely from this breed of horse",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  },{
    "id": 2012,
    "answer": "Standardbred",
    "question": "The American Trotting horse is the original name for this breed of horse",
    "value": 100,
    "airdate": null,
    "category_id": 101,
    "game_id": null,
    "invalid_count": null
  }
]
}`;
